# Juheeshwari Rajmohan

# Full Stack Web Developer

Full-stack web developer with over 8 years of experience analyzing, designing, developing, and integrating front-end & back-end-based applications. I possess a solid understanding of creating and enhancing user interfaces, conducting testing and debugging, and proficiently crafting web applications with responsive design using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, AngularJS, React, PHP, Python, Java and Go.Additionally, I bring over 2 years of experience in mobile app development, utilizing UNITY and Xcode for seamless gaming application.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **Lead Software Engineer (Remote)**

March 2021 - Present

i911, Miami, FL

- Developed major frontend features of a mobile application that allows users to track their fitness/outdoor activities and use different AR avatar filters as part of their journey experience using UNITY Xcode.
- Achieved a major milestone by refactoring the DEPRECATED code issue caused by the old version and a new version of Unity and XCode frameworks.
- Developed, and deployed the mobile applications using AWS services such as EC2, S3 and Django.
- Participated in code reviews of other developers' ensuring that all code complied 100% with coding standards & best practices.

## **University of Southern California**

September 2018 - March 2021

Senior Web Developer, Los Angeles, CA

- Developed, documented and maintained full-stack web applications in technologies like Golang with Iris, Gorilla Mux Framework, PHP, WordPress, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, AngularJS, and ReactJS for web development.
- Spearheaded transitions from WordPress, PHP sites to modern stack, reducing the latency by 35% and increasing database effectiveness by 70%.
- Developed and implemented Admin portal in Golang which directly helps HR department and communication manager to upload/edit or delete the content to the LIVE site with database connection.
- Maintained the CI/CD pipelines with AWS services and created Jenkins jobs to updating puppet at the master/slave.
- Followed AGILE Methodology for the software development process, part of the cross-functional team for the application development.
- Ensure applications security and ability to interact with multiple APIs and databases.

#### JLL

May 2018 – September 2018

Programmer Analyst, Los Angeles, CA

- Developed and executed research projects using PHP, MySQL, and Tableau.
- Maintained the production of data management, data integration processes.
- Developed and implemented a new scripting program with Python, SQL, and excel
  to save manual labor for real estate data entry and finding duplicates which
  boosted the performance by 65% saving over 50 hours of work.
- Participated in the design and development of technical solutions to ensure that business requirements are satisfied.

## CONTACT

- Los Angeles, CA (Open to relocate)
- +1-626-662-5214
- Website-Juheeshwari
- <u>lrjuheeshwari16@gmail.com</u>
- LinkedIn-Juheeshwari
- GitHub-Juheeshwari

#### **SKILLS**

#### Front End Development:

- HTML5
- · CSS3
- React
- jQuery
- Bootstrap
- Angular

#### **Technical Skills:**

- Java
- Python
- Go
- Node.js
- PHP
- MySQL
- Rest API
- Jenkins

#### **Cloud Platforms:**

- AWS
- Azure

## **EDUCATION**

- **Westcliff University** Master of Business Administration in Statistical Data Analysis (2021-2023): 3.89 GPA
- -California State University, Los Angeles -Master of Science in Computer Science (2015-2018): 3.45 GPA
- -Gujarat Technological University-Bachelor of Engineering in Computer Science (2010-2014): 3.76 GPA

#### **PROJECTS**

- <u>i911</u>
- <u>COVID-ARC</u>
- INI- USC
- NIIN
- CIC
- VCDAD